Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Just like that domineering Fifth Princess.
تماماً مثل تلك الأميرة الخامسة المتسلطة.
Coveting our Meng Mansion's little black pig.
أطمع في خنزير مينغ مانشن الأسود الصغير.
Stop playing dumb.
توقف عن التظاهر بالغباء.
Speak.
يتكلم.
Why are you disguised as a maid?
لماذا تتنكرين في زي خادمة؟
Coming to our Meng Mansion to steal a pig?
هل ستأتي إلى قصر مينغ لسرقة خنزير؟
A Lan is not playing dumb.
لا يتظاهر لان بالغباء.
And she didn't steal any pig.
ولم تسرق أي خنزير.
You look so foolish and dim-witted.
تبدو أحمقاً وغبياً للغاية.
A Lan is not dim-witted.
إن لان ليس غبياً.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
A Lan will take you to see a doctor.
سيأخذك لان إلى الطبيب.
He's sick.
إنه مريض.
He won't eat anything.
لن يأكل أي شيء.
He won't drink anything.
لن يشرب أي شيء.
He needs to see a doctor.
يحتاج إلى زيارة الطبيب.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
He seems to be eating just fine.
يبدو أنه يأكل بشكل جيد.
Guards!
حراس!
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Throw this girl out of the mansion.
أخرجوا هذه الفتاة من القصر.
Yes.
نعم.
Stop eating.
توقف عن الأكل.
Young Master!
يا سيدي الشاب!
Look!
ينظر!
Blackie really is sick.
بلاكي مريض حقاً.
Blackie looks...
بلاكي يبدو...
...a bit off today.
...ليس على ما يرام اليوم.
Perhaps he really is sick.
ربما يكون مريضاً بالفعل.
He really is sick.
إنه مريض حقاً.
It seems I wronged you.
يبدو أنني أخطأت في حقك.
Yinglu asked you to take care of Blackie.
طلب منك ينغلو أن تعتني بـ بلاكي.
And this is how you take care of him?
وهكذا تعتنون به؟
Cared for so well he won't eat or drink.
لقد حظي برعاية فائقة لدرجة أنه لا يأكل ولا يشرب.
Looking utterly miserable.
يبدو في غاية البؤس.
With such negligence...
مع هذا الإهمال...
...what use are you staying in Meng Mansion?
...ما فائدة إقامتك في قصر مينغ؟
Young Master! Young Master!
يا سيدي الشاب! يا سيدي الشاب!
Young Master!
يا سيدي الشاب!
Your servant won't leave.
لن يرحل خادمك.
Don't drive your servant out of the mansion.
لا تطرد خادمك من القصر.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
If I hadn't discovered it in time...
لو لم أكتشف ذلك في الوقت المناسب...
...Blackie would have been stolen by this girl.
...كانت هذه الفتاة ستسرق بلاكي.
Young Lady.
يا آنسة.
Blackie is sick.
بلاكي مريض.
A Lan is taking him to see a doctor.
يصطحبه لان إلى الطبيب.
A dimwit...
أحمق...
...but quite skilled at talking nonsense.
...لكنه بارعٌ جداً في قول الهراء.
Brother.
أخ.
She's not talking nonsense.
إنها لا تتحدث هراءً.
This is what the girl left in her room.
هذا ما تركته الفتاة في غرفتها.
"Blackie is sick."
"بلاكى مريض."
"A Lan will take him to see a doctor."
"سيأخذه أحد أفراد عائلة لان إلى الطبيب."
From now on, if Blackie gets sick...
من الآن فصاعدًا، إذا مرض بلاكي...
...you must tell me first.
...يجب أن تخبرني أولاً.
Understood?
مفهوم؟
Pass down the order.
مرر الأمر إلى الأجيال اللاحقة.
Starting today...
ابتداءً من اليوم...
...this girl is not allowed to take Blackie out of the mansion.
...لا يُسمح لهذه الفتاة بإخراج بلاكي من القصر.
If he gets lost...
إذا تاه...
...it's no trivial matter.
...إنها ليست مسألة تافهة.
Yes.
نعم.
Thank you, Young Master.
شكراً لك يا سيدي الشاب.
But your servant is not dim-witted.
لكن عبدك ليس غبياً.
She won't get lost.
لن تضل طريقها.
This young master is worried about...
هذا السيد الشاب قلق بشأن...
...Blackie getting lost.
...بلاكي يضيع.
Since Blackie is sick...
بما أن بلاكي مريض...
...then this young lady will take him...
...ثم ستأخذه هذه الشابة...
...to see a doctor.
...لزيارة الطبيب.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
How dare you stop me!
كيف تجرؤ على إيقافي!
Young Lady.
يا آنسة.
Before the master left, he ordered...
قبل أن يغادر السيد، أمر...
...that you are not to leave the mansion casually.
...أنه لا يجوز لك مغادرة القصر بشكل عرضي.
This young lady needs to leave on official business.
هذه الشابة بحاجة للمغادرة في مهمة رسمية.
The master specifically instructed...
أصدر المعلم تعليمات محددة...
...that even for official business, you cannot leave the mansion.
...حتى في الأمور الرسمية، لا يمكنك مغادرة القصر.
Fine, I won't go out then.
حسناً، لن أخرج إذاً.
Be smarter from now on.
كن أكثر ذكاءً من الآن فصاعدًا.
Be careful, or this young lady will throw you out.
احذر، وإلا ستطردك هذه الشابة.
Blackie will stay in my room tonight.
سيبقى بلاكي في غرفتي الليلة.
You feed him later.
ستطعمه لاحقاً.
Blackie.
بلاكي.
Blackie, be good.
بلاكي، كن مطيعاً.
Eat.
يأكل.
Being naughty again, are we?
هل عدنا إلى سلوكنا المشاغب؟
Haven't seen you in a few days...
لم أرك منذ بضعة أيام...
...and you've already sunk to being a maid in Meng Mansion.
...وقد انحدرتِ بالفعل إلى مستوى الخادمة في قصر مينغ.
Truly impressive.
مثير للإعجاب حقاً.
Your anger subsided quite quickly.
هدأ غضبك بسرعة كبيرة.
It's rare to see you in a predicament.
من النادر أن أراك في مأزق.
Naturally, I had to come see the show.
وبطبيعة الحال، كان عليّ أن أحضر لمشاهدة العرض.
Let me tell you...
دعني أخبرك...
...I already know...
...أعلم ذلك بالفعل...
...when Blackie will meet his end.
...عندما يلقى بلاكي حتفه.
Oh really?
أوه حقًا؟
You have that ability?
هل لديك هذه القدرة؟
Look here.
انظر هنا.
Blackie has a dark shadow between his brows.
يوجد ظل داكن بين حاجبي بلاكي.
His appetite isn't great either.
شهيته ليست جيدة أيضاً.
How could a black pig's brow *not* be black?
كيف يمكن أن يكون جبين خنزير أسود *ليس* أسود؟
According to my intuition...
بحسب حدسي...
...Blackie's time of death is approaching.
...حان وقت وفاة بلاكي.
If nothing unexpected happens...
إذا لم يحدث شيء غير متوقع...
...it will be within the next few days.
...سيحدث ذلك خلال الأيام القليلة القادمة.
What "next few days"?
ماذا تعني "الأيام القليلة القادمة"؟
It's still a long way off.
لا يزال الطريق طويلاً.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Then I'm relieved.
ثم أشعر بالارتياح.
You're too cunning.
أنت ماكر للغاية.
You actually tricked me into talking.
لقد خدعتني بالفعل لأتحدث.
You're the only one allowed to trick me?
أنت الوحيد المسموح له بخداعي؟
I'm not allowed to trick you back?
أليس من حقي أن أخدعك بالمقابل؟
You...
أنت...
Good luck to you.
أتمنى لك التوفيق.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Blackie.
بلاكي.
Yuwen Xiu must be anxiously sending people to search for me everywhere.
لا بد أن يوين شيو يرسل الناس بقلق للبحث عني في كل مكان.
Should I send him a message...
هل أرسل له رسالة؟
...to let him know I'm safe?
...لأُعلمه أنني بخير؟
Big Brother!
الأخ الأكبر!
Young Master Xiu!
السيد الشاب شيو!
Big Brother! Young Master Xiu!
أخي الكبير! السيد الشاب شيو!
The lord is still sleeping.
الرب لا يزال نائماً.
Big Brother!
الأخ الأكبر!
You mustn't...
لا يجب عليك...
I was wrong!
كنت مخطئاً!
Calm your anger!
اهدأ من غضبك!
I... Big Brother, please calm down!
أنا... أخي الكبير، أرجوك اهدأ!
I was wrong, I was wrong!
كنت مخطئاً، كنت مخطئاً!
I...
أنا...
Young Master Xiu.
السيد الشاب شيو.
It's not like you don't know...
ليس الأمر كما لو أنك لا تعرف...
...when the lord is sleeping...
...عندما يكون الرب نائماً...
...he dislikes being disturbed the most.
...إنه يكره أن يُزعج أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
How could you forget?
كيف يُمكنك أن تنسى؟
I...
أنا...
I was just anxious for a moment.
شعرت بالقلق للحظة.
I just...
أنا فقط...
Big brother
الأخ الأكبر
I've looked everywhere
لقد بحثت في كل مكان
and couldn't find her anywhere.
ولم يتمكن من العثور عليها في أي مكان.
Can the Fifth Princess survive outside the palace?
هل تستطيع الأميرة الخامسة البقاء على قيد الحياة خارج القصر؟
Will she have enough to eat and wear?
هل سيكون لديها ما يكفي من الطعام والملابس؟
What if she encounters ruffians?
ماذا لو واجهت أشراراً؟
The world is a dangerous place.
العالم مكان خطير.
She's just a delicate woman.
إنها امرأة رقيقة للغاية.
Big brother...
الأخ الأكبر...
Please, help me out.
أرجوكم ساعدوني.
I sent word to the palace
أرسلتُ رسالةً إلى القصر
saying A Lan would stay at my mansion for a couple of days
قال: "سيقيم آلان في قصري لبضعة أيام".
and return her after the Drunken Immortal Tavern opens.
وأعدها بعد افتتاح حانة "الخالد السكران".
That's how I covered it up for now.
هكذا أخفيت الأمر مؤقتاً.
If we still can't find her...
إذا لم نتمكن من العثور عليها بعد...
then... then I'm done for!
ثم... ثم انتهى أمري!
Alright, I'll help you this once.
حسناً، سأساعدك هذه المرة.
This is the note received this morning.
هذه هي الرسالة التي استلمناها هذا الصباح.
Seventh Cousin,
ابن العم السابع،
guess where A Lan is hiding?
خمن أين يختبئ آلان؟
Did you find the person who delivered the note?
هل عثرت على الشخص الذي سلم الرسالة؟
Give the order.
أعطِ الأمر.
Have all Shadow Guards search for the Fifth Princess.
اطلب من جميع حراس الظل البحث عن الأميرة الخامسة.
My lord,
سيدي،
since the Fifth Princess could send someone with a note,
بما أن الأميرة الخامسة تستطيع إرسال شخص ما برسالة،
it means she's at least safe for now.
هذا يعني أنها على الأقل بأمان في الوقت الحالي.
There's no need
لا داعي لذلك
to mobilize all Shadow Guards, is there?
هل هناك حاجة لتعبئة جميع حراس الظل؟
Before tonight,
قبل الليلة،
you must find the Fifth Princess.
يجب عليك العثور على الأميرة الخامسة.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Where are Ke Ren and Blackie?
أين كي رين وبلاكي؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Let this young master give you a hug.
دع هذا الشاب يعانقك.
You seem to have gained a lot of weight lately.
يبدو أنك اكتسبت الكثير من الوزن مؤخراً.
Does the young master not like it?
ألا يعجب السيد الشاب ذلك؟
It's good to be plump.
من الجيد أن تكون ممتلئ الجسم.
It feels nicer to the touch.
ملمسه أجمل.
As long as the young master is pleased.
طالما أن السيد الشاب راضٍ.
Morals are declining,
الأخلاق تتدهور،
and people's hearts are not what they used to be.
وقلوب الناس لم تعد كما كانت.
Meng Shaojue, in broad daylight,
منغ شاوجوي، في وضح النهار،
right in front of Blackie, with Ke Ren...
أمام بلاكي مباشرة، مع كي رين...
What have you been eating lately
ماذا كنت تأكل مؤخراً؟
to get this fat?
كيف أصبح بهذا الوزن؟
The same as usual.
كما هو معتاد.
I don't know why I gained weight.
لا أعرف لماذا زاد وزني.
Oh, he was talking about Blackie.
أوه، كان يتحدث عن بلاكي.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Young master!
يا سيدي الشاب!
It's you.
أنت هو.
So idle
عاطلون عن العمل
that you come here to eavesdrop?
هل أتيت إلى هنا للتنصت؟
Young master!
يا سيدي الشاب!
You molested your servant!
لقد اعتدت على خادمك!
With your looks,
بمظهرك،
what's there for this young master to molest?
ما الذي يمكن لهذا الشاب أن يتحرش به؟
Young master,
سيد شاب،
it's time for Blackie's bath.
حان وقت استحمام بلاكي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Brother!
أخ!
I have important business outside the mansion today.
لديّ أعمال مهمة خارج القصر اليوم.
Can you talk to the guards for me?
هل يمكنك التحدث إلى الحراس نيابة عني؟
They'll definitely listen to you.
سيستمعون إليك بالتأكيد.
What important business could you have?
ما هي أهم الأعمال التي يمكنك القيام بها؟
The poetry book Father told me to copy is lost.
كتاب الشعر الذي طلب مني أبي نسخه قد ضاع.
I'm going to buy a new one.
سأشتري واحدة جديدة.
I have several more in my room.
لديّ المزيد في غرفتي.
Go get one later.
اذهب واحصل على واحد لاحقاً.
Brother...
أخ...
Young master,
سيد شاب،
the Chief Grand Secretary and the Fourth Princess have arrived.
وصل كبير أمناء السر والأميرة الرابعة.
What are they here for?
لماذا هم هنا؟
Young Master Meng.
السيد الشاب مينغ.
The Chief Grand Secretary and I are here
أنا وكبير أمناء السر هنا
to investigate the incident involving the assassin from the Flying Immortal Pavilion.
للتحقيق في الحادثة التي تورط فيها القاتل من جناح الخالدين الطائرين.
Were you at the Flying Immortal Pavilion that night,
هل كنت في جناح فلاينج إمورتال تلك الليلة؟
Young Master Meng? Did you notice anyone suspicious?
سيد مينغ الشاب؟ هل لاحظت أي شخص مريب؟
Think carefully.
فكر جيداً.
Actually, yes.
في الواقع، نعم.
Who?
من؟
Why, it's naturally the ruthless one
لماذا، إنه بطبيعة الحال الشخص القاسي؟
who wouldn't even spare a little black pig.
من الذي لا يرحم حتى خنزيرًا أسود صغيرًا؟
Chief Grand Secretary.
رئيس السكرتارية الكبرى.
The Chief Grand Secretary is highly capable,
يتمتع كبير أمناء السر بكفاءة عالية،
and a perfect match for the vicious, domineering Fifth Princess.
وهي مناسبة تمامًا للأميرة الخامسة الشرسة والمتسلطة.
Truly a perfect pair.
ثنائي مثالي حقاً.
Vicious and domineering?
شرس ومتسلط؟
Young Master Meng,
السيد الشاب مينغ،
you mustn't speak carelessly.
لا يجب أن تتحدث بتهور.
Isn't that the truth?
أليست هذه هي الحقيقة؟
For you to openly slander the Fifth Princess
أن تقوم علناً بتشويه سمعة الأميرة الخامسة
is not appropriate, is it?
هذا غير مناسب، أليس كذلك؟
And meeting dance girls at the Flying Immortal Pavilion at night—
ومقابلة راقصات في جناح فلاينج إمورتال ليلاً؟
does the Chief Grand Secretary find that appropriate?
هل يرى كبير أمناء السر أن ذلك مناسب؟
Meeting dance girls at night?
مقابلة راقصات ليلاً؟
Since Young Master Meng has no useful information,
بما أن السيد الشاب مينغ لا يملك أي معلومات مفيدة،
we shall take our leave.
سنغادر الآن.
Young Master Meng,
السيد الشاب مينغ،
I heard your mansion has a
سمعت أن قصرك فيه...
rare Sacred Fruit Tree from the southern mountains,
شجرة فاكهة مقدسة نادرة من الجبال الجنوبية،
seen only once in a hundred years.
لا يُرى إلا مرة واحدة كل مئة عام.
Could you show it to me?
هل يمكنك أن تريني إياه؟
Ke Ren, brother was just looking for you.
كي رين، أخي كان يبحث عنك.
You should go quickly.
يجب أن تذهب بسرعة.
Yes, miss.
نعم يا آنسة.
Heaven helps me!
يا ربّي ساعدني!
I didn't expect you to be so interested in the Sacred Fruit Tree.
لم أتوقع أن تكون مهتمًا جدًا بشجرة الفاكهة المقدسة.
Brother!
أخ!
My lord,
سيدي،
this way, please.
من هنا، من فضلك.
Perhaps we should see the fruit tree another day.
ربما ينبغي أن نرى شجرة الفاكهة في يوم آخر.
We should focus on the investigation of the Flying Immortal Pavilion assassin first.
ينبغي أن نركز أولاً على التحقيق في قضية قاتل جناح الخلود الطائر.
Imperial Sister,
الأخت الإمبراطورية،
a little delay won't hurt.
لن يضر التأخير قليلاً.
Yuwen Xiu!
يوين شيوى!
Ouch!
آخ!
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Come out now!
اخرج الآن!
Must I personally invite you out?
هل يجب عليّ أن أدعوك شخصياً للخروج؟
Come here at once!
تعال إلى هنا فوراً!
Yinglu!
ينجلو!
Take that basket off.
انزع تلك السلة.
Pay your respects to the Fourth Princess and the Chief Grand Secretary.
قدموا احترامكم للأميرة الرابعة وكبير السكرتيرين.
Brother,
أخ،
I'm Ke Ren.
أنا كي رين.
I'm Ke Ren too.
أنا كي رين أيضاً.
Young Master Meng,
السيد الشاب مينغ،
the people in your mansion are quite amusing.
الناس في قصرك مسلّون للغاية.
Please excuse us, Fourth Princess.
أرجو المعذرة يا أميرة الرابعة.
Enough, Ke Ren.
كفى يا كي رين.
Take the basket off.
انزع السلة.
Hurry up and take it off!
أسرع واخلعه!
Brother Blackie,
أخي بلاكي،
sorry about this.
أعتذر عن هذا.
Blackie ran away!
هرب بلاكي!
Go, hurry and catch Blackie!
انطلق، أسرع واقبض على بلاكي!
Quickly!
بسرعة!
My younger sister is mischievous.
أختي الصغرى مشاغبة.
Please excuse her.
أرجو المعذرة.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Why are you hiding in that vat with Blackie?
لماذا تختبئ في ذلك الحوض مع بلاكي؟
Quiet.
هادئ.
Blackie likes to sleep there.
بلاكي يحب النوم هناك.
What a dummy.
يا له من أحمق.
About me climbing the wall...
عن تسلقي الجدار...
You mustn't tell anyone.
لا يجب أن تخبر أحداً.
Understood?
مفهوم؟
Alright, alright.
حسناً، حسناً.
Go find Blackie now.
اذهب وابحث عن بلاكي الآن.
Blackie.
بلاكي.
About meeting the dancer at night...
عن لقاء الراقصة ليلاً...
Elder Cousin.
ابن العم الأكبر.
What do you have to say?
ما رأيك؟
You are currently engaged to A Lan.
أنتِ مخطوبة حالياً لـ أ. لان.
Meeting a dancer at night...
مقابلة راقصة ليلاً...
Where does that leave A Lan?
ماذا يعني ذلك بالنسبة لـ "إيه لان"؟
It's not what you think.
الأمر ليس كما تظن.
A Lan is naive and innocent now.
أصبحت لان ساذجة وبريئة الآن.
If you, Elder Cousin, are a womanizer...
إذا كنت يا ابن العم الأكبر زير نساء...
A philanderer who leaves a trail of broken hearts...
رجلٌ زير نساء يترك وراءه سلسلة من القلوب المحطمة...
I will do everything in my power...
سأبذل قصارى جهدي...
To stop your marriage to A Lan.
لإيقاف زواجك من أ. لان.
The Fourth Princess will not get that chance.
لن تحصل الأميرة الرابعة على تلك الفرصة.
As for the others who were at the Flying Immortal Pavilion...
أما بالنسبة للآخرين الذين كانوا في جناح الخالد الطائر...
I'll trouble the Fourth Princess to investigate them.
سأكلف الأميرة الرابعة بالتحقيق في الأمر.
Sir, how did it go?
سيدي، كيف سارت الأمور؟
The Meng Mansion is heavily guarded.
قصر مينغ محمي بشكل كبير.
I'll come again tonight.
سأعود الليلة.
And the Fifth Princess?
والأميرة الخامسة؟
Any news?
أي أخبار؟
I had the Shadow Guards investigate.
كلفتُ حراس الظل بالتحقيق.
We only know...
كل ما نعرفه...
The Fifth Princess was last seen at Shunshun Gambling Den.
شوهدت الأميرة الخامسة آخر مرة في وكر قمار شونشون.
How many men did you send?
كم عدد الرجال الذين أرسلتهم؟
Don't worry about that, sir.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك يا سيدي.
Just one.
واحد فقط.
One?
واحد؟
I've thought it over carefully.
لقد فكرت في الأمر ملياً.
Sir, you don't like the Fifth Princess.
سيدي، أنت لا تحب الأميرة الخامسة.
And you're eager to cancel the engagement with her.
وأنت تتوق إلى إلغاء خطوبتك منها.
So how could you...
فكيف يمكنك...
Truly care about the Fifth Princess's safety?
هل تهتم حقاً بسلامة الأميرة الخامسة؟
When you told me to mobilize all Shadow Guards...
عندما طلبت مني تعبئة جميع حراس الظل...
That was merely...
كان ذلك مجرد...
Empty words for Young Master Xiu's benefit.
كلام فارغ لمصلحة السيد الشاب شيو.
Rest assured, sir.
اطمئن يا سيدي.
I understand completely.
أفهم تماماً.
If there's still no news of the Fifth Princess by tonight...
إذا لم ترد أي أخبار عن الأميرة الخامسة حتى الليلة...
You will depart for the Northern Territories.
ستغادرون إلى الأقاليم الشمالية.
This...
هذا...
Sir...
سيد...
The Northern Territories, they...
الأقاليم الشمالية، هم...
They're covered in snow year-round.
إنها مغطاة بالثلوج على مدار السنة.
Not suitable for someone as cold-averse as me.
غير مناسب لشخص مثلي يكره البرد.
Precisely because it's unsuitable, I'm sending you.
لأنني أرسلك تحديداً لأنها غير مناسبة.
Sir!
سيد!
Then...
ثم...
Could the Fifth Princess...
هل يمكن للأميرة الخامسة...
Have gone to work as a maid in some mansion?
هل ذهبت للعمل كخادمة في قصر ما؟
She's not actually foolish.
هي ليست حمقاء في الواقع.
Why would she give up being a princess...
لماذا ستتخلى عن كونها أميرة...
To be a maid?
أن تصبح خادمة؟
Move this wine inside.
انقل هذا النبيذ إلى الداخل.
Right away!
فورا!
Be careful!
احرص!
Wipe this cleaner.
امسح هذا المنظف.
Got it!
فهمتها!
Stop working.
توقف عن العمل.
Go home and rest.
اذهب إلى المنزل واسترح.
Huh?
هاه؟
What's wrong, young master?
ما الخطب يا سيدي الشاب؟
I'm in a bad mood.
أنا في مزاج سيء.
I don't want to open.
لا أريد أن أفتح.
But...
لكن...
Seventh Cousin!
ابن العم السابع!
A Zi.
أوه زي.
Everyone, stop working.
توقفوا جميعاً عن العمل.
Go inside.
ادخل إلى الداخل.
I was just on my way to investigate the Flying Immortal Pavilion incident.
كنت في طريقي للتحقيق في حادثة جناح الخالد الطائر.
And happened to pass by.
ومرّ من هناك بالصدفة.
Is A Lan here?
هل لان هنا؟
I'll go see her.
سأذهب لرؤيتها.
A Lan is still sleeping.
لا يزال لان نائماً.
Don't wake her.
لا توقظها.
Your tavern opens tomorrow, right?
حانتك ستفتح غداً، أليس كذلك؟
Tell A Lan...
أخبر لان...
I'll be here tomorrow too.
سأكون هنا غداً أيضاً.
Aren't you investigating the assassin?
ألا تحققون في أمر القاتل؟
It's fine if you don't come.
لا بأس إن لم تأتِ.
For my Seventh Cousin's tavern opening...
بمناسبة افتتاح حانة ابن عمي السابع...
Of course I must attend.
بالطبع يجب أن أحضر.
I have other matters, I must go.
لدي أمور أخرى، يجب أن أذهب.
Young master...
سيد شاب...
Are we still opening tomorrow?
هل سنفتح أبوابنا غداً؟
Don't run!
لا تركض!
Stop right there!
توقف هنا!
Blackie.
بلاكي.
So it really is you.
إذن أنت هو فعلاً.
In the dead of night...
في جوف الليل...
What is Your Excellency doing?
ماذا يفعل فخامتكم؟
What is the Fifth Princess doing?
ماذا تفعل الأميرة الخامسة؟
I certainly didn't expect...
بالتأكيد لم أتوقع...
The Fifth Princess to become a maid at the Meng Mansion.
الأميرة الخامسة التي ستصبح خادمة في قصر مينغ.
I didn't expect either...
لم أتوقع ذلك أيضاً...
Your Excellency to take up trespassing.
يا صاحب السعادة، أن تتناول موضوع التعدي على الممتلكات.
After not seeing you for a few days...
بعد غيابك لبضعة أيام...
You've become quite sharp-tongued.
لقد أصبحتَ سليطي اللسان للغاية.
Your Excellency.
صاحب السعادة.
You mind your business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
I'll mind mine.
سأهتم بشؤوني.
Why come to the Meng Mansion?
لماذا تأتي إلى قصر مينغ؟
A twist of fate.
تقلبات القدر.
Just came to the Meng Mansion for fun.
جئت إلى قصر مينغ لمجرد التسلية.
Playing at being a maid.
تمثيل دور الخادمة.
The palace is so boring.
القصر ممل للغاية.
I...
أنا...
Zi Xiu is sending people everywhere to look for you.
زي شيو يرسل الناس في كل مكان للبحث عنك.
Later, I'll take you back to the palace.
سأعيدك إلى القصر لاحقاً.
I'll return on my own in a couple of days.
سأعود بمفردي خلال يومين.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't reveal my whereabouts.
سأكون ممتناً لو لم تكشف عن مكاني.
The Meng Mansion is quite lively tonight.
قصر مينغ يعج بالحيوية هذه الليلة.
Assassin!
قاتل!
There's an assassin!
هناك قاتل!
Over here!
هنا!
Quickly!
بسرعة!
The assassin went that way!
لقد سلك القاتل ذلك الطريق!
This way, hurry!
من هنا، أسرع!
The assassin outside, is he one of your men?
هل القاتل الموجود بالخارج أحد رجالك؟
My men aren't that clumsy.
رجالي ليسوا بهذا القدر من الخرق.
To be discovered so easily.
أن يتم اكتشافها بهذه السهولة.
Could it be Prince Ning's men?
هل يمكن أن يكونوا رجال الأمير نينغ؟
Your Excellency should hurry and figure out how to leave.
ينبغي على فخامتكم الإسراع في إيجاد طريقة للمغادرة.
Young master!
يا سيدي الشاب!
The assassin is coming this way!
القاتل قادم من هذا الاتجاه!
Quick!
سريع!
Search the area!
ابحث في المنطقة!
Young master, the assassin is here!
يا سيدي الشاب، القاتل هنا!
He hasn't gone far!
لم يذهب بعيداً!
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Halt!
وقف!
He's gone.
لقد رحل.
It's getting late.
لقد تأخر الوقت.
Your Excellency should leave as soon as possible.
ينبغي على فخامتكم المغادرة في أسرع وقت ممكن.
If you want to play,
إذا كنت ترغب في اللعب،
I promise you
أعدك
I won't reveal your whereabouts for now.
لن أكشف عن مكان وجودك في الوقت الحالي.
If you haven't returned to the palace in three days,
إذا لم تعد إلى القصر خلال ثلاثة أيام،
I will forcibly bring you back.
سأعيدك بالقوة.
After all, Meng Mansion is not as safe as the palace.
ففي النهاية، قصر مينغ ليس آمناً مثل القصر.
Fine, I understand.
حسناً، فهمت.
Take care, my lord.
اعتنِ بنفسك يا سيدي.
None of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Your Highness, Meng Mansion is heavily guarded.
صاحب السمو، قصر مينغ يخضع لحراسة مشددة.
Barging in to search for the map would be unwise.
سيكون اقتحام المكان للبحث عن الخريطة أمراً غير حكيم.
You may withdraw to tend to your wounds.
يمكنك الانسحاب لمعالجة جروحك.
Yes.
نعم.
It seems then
يبدو إذن
it's better to wait until Meng Shaojue's birthday
من الأفضل الانتظار حتى عيد ميلاد مينغ شاوجو
to infiltrate Meng Mansion and search for the map.
للتسلل إلى قصر مينغ والبحث عن الخريطة.
My lord.
سيدي.
I have failed in my duty.
لقد فشلت في أداء واجبي.
I have yet to locate the Fifth Princess.
لم أعثر بعد على الأميرة الخامسة.
My lord.
سيدي.
Have you found the map?
هل عثرت على الخريطة؟
It's fine. Have some tea first.
لا بأس. تناول بعض الشاي أولاً.
This tea,
هذا الشاي،
I had someone replace the pot every half-stick of incense,
كنت أطلب من أحدهم استبدال وعاء البخور كلما استخدمت نصف عود بخور.
so you'd have a hot cup as soon as you returned.
لذا ستحصل على كوب ساخن بمجرد عودتك.
Why are you still at the mansion so late?
لماذا ما زلت في القصر في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
Are you hungry, my lord?
هل أنت جائع يا سيدي؟
I'll go to the kitchen to see if there's any food.
سأذهب إلى المطبخ لأرى إن كان هناك أي طعام.
You can depart for the Northern Territories.
يمكنك المغادرة إلى الأقاليم الشمالية.
My lord...
يا سيدي...
I don't want to go.
لا أريد الذهاب.
I understand.
أفهم.
I'll go pack my things now.
سأذهب الآن لأحزم أمتعتي.
The Fifth Princess has been found.
تم العثور على الأميرة الخامسة.
Really?
حقًا؟
My lord!
يا سيدي!
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Does that mean I don't have to go to the Northern Territories?
هل هذا يعني أنني لست مضطراً للذهاب إلى الأقاليم الشمالية؟
Inform Zixiu
أبلغ Zixiu
that the Fifth Princess has been found.
تم العثور على الأميرة الخامسة.
She is perfectly safe.
إنها بأمان تام.
I will bring her back to the palace within three days.
سأعيدها إلى القصر في غضون ثلاثة أيام.
I'll see to it immediately.
سأهتم بالأمر فوراً.
Brother.
أخ.
I heard there was an assassin in the mansion last night.
سمعت أن هناك قاتلاً مأجوراً في القصر الليلة الماضية.
What kind of assassin is so brazen
أي نوع من القتلة يتسم بهذه الجرأة؟
as to dare come to our Meng Mansion?
كيف يجرؤ أحد على المجيء إلى قصر مينغ الخاص بنا؟
Brother,
أخ،
leave this to me.
اترك هذا الأمر لي.
I'll go dig him out.
سأذهب لأحفره وأخرجه من هنا.
Finish copying this poetry collection first.
أكمل نسخ هذه المجموعة الشعرية أولاً.
From now on, don't let this girl take care of Blackie.
من الآن فصاعدًا، لا تدع هذه الفتاة تعتني بـ"بلاكي".
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Your servant enjoys taking care of Blackie.
خادمك يستمتع بالاعتناء بـ"بلاكي".
That's right, brother.
هذا صحيح يا أخي.
Blackie seems to like her too.
يبدو أن بلاكي معجب بها أيضاً.
What does a pig know about liking or disliking?
ما الذي يعرفه الخنزير عن الإعجاب أو الكراهية؟
Blackie will stay in my courtyard from now on.
سيبقى بلاكي في فناء منزلي من الآن فصاعدًا.
Keqing.
كيكينغ.
Yes.
نعم.
That servant Shuncai still hasn't been found?
ألم يتم العثور على الخادم شونكاي حتى الآن؟
He truly has no conscience.
إنه حقاً بلا ضمير.
Brother treated him well,
كان أخوه يعامله معاملة حسنة.
yet he stole your dagger.
لكنه سرق خنجرك.
That was the last birthday gift
كانت تلك آخر هدية عيد ميلاد
Mother gave you before she passed.
أعطتك إياها والدتك قبل وفاتها.
Shuncai stole the dagger,
سرق شونكاي الخنجر،
so he'll surely pawn it.
لذلك سيقوم برهنها بالتأكيد.
Go check the major pawnshops.
اذهب وتفقد محلات الرهونات الكبرى.
Yes, Young Master.
نعم، سيدي الشاب.
Brother,
أخ،
aren't you going to that place today...
ألن تذهب إلى ذلك المكان اليوم؟
the Drunken Immortal Tavern?
حانة الخالد السكران؟
You want to go too?
هل تريد الذهاب أيضاً؟
Of course not!
بالطبع لا!
I still have to copy the poetry collection.
ما زلتُ بحاجة إلى نسخ مجموعة الشعر.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Your servant doesn't want to leave the mansion.
خادمك لا يريد مغادرة القصر.
Your servant wants to take care of Blackie.
خادمك يريد أن يعتني بـ"بلاكي".
Keep your voice down.
اخفض صوتك.
If we're discovered, we won't get out.
إذا تم اكتشافنا، فلن نتمكن من الخروج.
Hurry.
عجل.
The guards will be back soon.
سيعود الحراس قريباً.
If you dare leak my affairs
إذا تجرأت على تسريب شؤوني
like the other maids did,
كما فعلت الخادمات الأخريات،
this young lady will definitely throw you out.
هذه الشابة ستطردك بالتأكيد.
Your servant will obey you in everything, Miss.
سيطيعك خادمك في كل شيء يا آنسة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
In all these years,
طوال هذه السنوات،
when have the Four Young Masters of Yunmi ever gathered?
متى اجتمع السادة الأربعة الشباب من يونمي؟
Exactly!
بالضبط!
How come the opening of the Drunken Immortal Tavern
كيف تم افتتاح حانة الخالد السكران
can bring all Four Young Masters together?
هل يستطيع جمع الأساتذة الشباب الأربعة معًا؟
That's naturally because
هذا أمر طبيعي لأن
the owner of the Drunken Immortal Tavern...
صاحب حانة "السكران الخالد"...
The Four Young Masters are here!
وصل الأساتذة الشباب الأربعة!
Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters!
أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب!
The Four Young Masters of Yunmi really have a grand presence.
يتمتع الأساتذة الشباب الأربعة في يونمي بحضور مهيب حقًا.
Don't let brother find us.
لا تدع أخي يعثر علينا.
Lord He.
يا رب.
Eldest Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Fifth...
خامساً...
Will that thing really return to the palace in three days?
هل سيعود ذلك الشيء إلى القصر فعلاً خلال ثلاثة أيام؟
Mm-hmm.
ممم.
When the Fourth Princess asks...
عندما تسأل الأميرة الرابعة...
Don't worry, Eldest Brother.
لا تقلق يا أخي الأكبر.
Four Young Masters!
أربعة أساتذة شباب!
Young Master Xiu!
السيد الشاب شيو!
I wrote a poem for you!
لقد كتبت قصيدة لك!
Young Master Meng!
السيد الشاب مينغ!
I wrote you a letter!
لقد كتبت لك رسالة!
I wrote a letter too!
لقد كتبت رسالة أيضاً!
This is mine!
هذا ملكي!
Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters!
أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب!
Lord He is indeed as the rumors say:
الرب هو بالفعل كما تقول الشائعات:
Majestic and peerless in the world.
مهيب وفريد ​​من نوعه في العالم.
Miss Meng is actually a stan of He Lianchen.
الآنسة مينغ هي في الواقع من أشد المعجبين بهي ليانتشن.
Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters!
أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب!
Young Master Meng, this is my letter!
السيد الشاب مينغ، هذه رسالتي!
A Zi, you're here.
أهلاً بك يا زي.
Where's A Lan?
أين شبكة لان؟
A Lan? She knew Eldest Brother was coming today,
لان؟ كانت تعلم أن الأخ الأكبر سيأتي اليوم.
so she was too excited to sleep last night.
لذا كانت متحمسة للغاية لدرجة أنها لم تستطع النوم الليلة الماضية.
She only fell asleep this morning.
لم تنم إلا هذا الصباح.
I really couldn't bear to wake her.
لم أستطع حقاً أن أتحمل إيقاظها.
Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters!
أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب!
A Lan is so devoted to him,
إن آلان مخلصة له للغاية،
yet he still meets with dancing girls at night.
ومع ذلك، لا يزال يلتقي بالراقصات ليلاً.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters! Four Young Masters!
أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب! أربعة أساتذة شباب!
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Eldest Brother.
الأخ الأكبر.
Brother Meng, Brother He.
الأخ مينغ، الأخ هي.
Go on.
هيا.
Where did you come from? What are you doing?
من أين أتيت؟ ماذا تفعل؟
Lord Yuwen!
اللورد يووين!
This young lady didn't mean to!
لم تقصد هذه الشابة ذلك!
If apologies were useful,
إذا كانت الاعتذارات مفيدة،
what would we need constables and bailiffs for?
لماذا نحتاج إلى رجال الشرطة والمحضرين؟
Come, please.
تفضل، من فضلك.
Fourth Young Master! Fourth Young Master! Fourth Young Master!
السيد الشاب الرابع! السيد الشاب الرابع! السيد الشاب الرابع!
As expected of Lord He.
كما هو متوقع من اللورد هي.
Honorable and impartial.
شريف ونزيه.
Young lady.
يا آنسة.
The young master will find out.
سيكتشف السيد الشاب ذلك.
We've changed our clothes and are wearing veils.
لقد غيرنا ملابسنا ونرتدي الحجاب.
How would my brother find out?
كيف سيكتشف أخي الأمر؟
Fourth Young Master! Fourth Young Master! Fourth Young Master!
السيد الشاب الرابع! السيد الشاب الرابع! السيد الشاب الرابع!
Thank you, everyone.
شكراً لكم جميعاً.
Today, my Drunken Immortal Tavern opens.
اليوم، سيتم افتتاح حانة "الخالد السكران" الخاصة بي.
All food and drink are half price.
جميع المأكولات والمشروبات بنصف السعر.
Great! Great! Great!
رائع! رائع! رائع!
Come on in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Excellent! Excellent! Excellent!
ممتاز! ممتاز! ممتاز!
Everyone.
الجميع.
Please, come inside.
تفضل بالدخول.
You three, please.
من فضلكم، أنتم الثلاثة.
Young master.
سيد شاب.
I just found out.
لقد علمت بذلك للتو.
Yuwen Xiu specifically prepared for Meng Shaojue...
أعد Yuwen Xiu خصيصًا لـ Meng Shaojue...
...a pot of wine.
...إناء من النبيذ.
I put the item in that pot of wine.
وضعتُ الشيء في قدر النبيذ.
Last time, Meng Shaojue ruined my plans.
في المرة الماضية، أفسد منغ شاوجوي خططي.
This time, I'll make him know...
هذه المرة، سأجعله يعرف...
...this young master's power.
...قوة هذا السيد الشاب.